{"data":[{"question":"The mother smiled happy and took the baby in her arms.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"mother","b":"happy","c":"took","d":"in","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Happy-> happily","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"30","type":"1"},{"question":"We are going to invite a person who has special skill showing you how to control this machine.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"to invite","b":"who","c":"showing","d":"to control","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Showing-> to show","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"30","type":"1"},{"question":"Amanda finally managed to get a good job, and so does Nancy.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"finally","b":"to get","c":"and","d":"so does","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- So does-> so did","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"30","type":"1"},{"question":"How much times did Lan and Mai have to do the experiment?\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"How much","b":"did Lan and Mai","c":"have to","d":"do","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- How much-> how many","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"30","type":"1"},{"question":"A lunch of soup and sandwiches do not appeal to all of the students.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"A","b":"of soup","c":"do not","d":"appeal to all of","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Do not-> does not","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"30","type":"1"},{"question":"Mrs. Stevens, along with her cousins from Mexico, are planning to attend the festivities.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"with her cousins","b":"from","c":"are","d":"to attend","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Are-> is","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"30","type":"1"},{"question":"How long is it since they buy the house?\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"How long","b":"is","c":"since","d":"buy","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- Buy-> bought","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"30","type":"1"},{"question":"We won't get to the airport in least than 30 minutes.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"won't get","b":"to","c":"in","d":"least than","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- Least than-> least","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"30","type":"1"},{"question":"Despite knowing the area well, I got be lost.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Despite","b":"knowing","c":"be","d":"lost","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Be-> x","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"30","type":"1"},{"question":"The men continued to feel unsafely until he crossed the border.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"men","b":"continued","c":"unsafely","d":"crossed","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Unsafely-> unsafe","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"30","type":"1"}]}